(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T21:12:26.250385",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive GAMERS fes. 超ゲマズ2 day1
[hololive GAMERS fes. Super Gamers 2 Day 1]
ホロライブ ゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) we are gamers !
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers!
こーん！とキツネが登場
Kon! A fox appears,
白髪ケモミミ 白上フブキ です
White-haired kemonomimi, Shirakami Fubuki!
スッとん込んでちゃ始まらない
Can't start without rushing in!
君もスコン部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sconbu too!
hi friends !
Hi friends!
古今東西こうん茶をちょっとだい
A cup of Kohun tea from past and present,
AIじゃないし得意はMC
Not AI, and my forte is MC!
赤い恋より金色の鯉が推し
More than red romance, golden carp is best!
うちうちうちだょ 大神ミオだよ
That's right, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ 狼みおーん！
Black-haired kemonomimi, wolf Mio-n!
ツッコんで止めますlike a ママ
Stopping the tsukkomi like a mama,
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop, gege
つまり実はponってコト！？
Meaning I'm actually a bit pon!?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of quick little steps,
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future through tarot cards.
ホラーゲームはやしたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよBダッシュ
Come play with us, B-Dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げて
Aiming to clear, leveling up,
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices, simulation,
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Gaming is really fun, huh?
(G-A-M-E-R-S) we are gamers !
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers!
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
いっくよー もぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Here we go, mogu-mogu~ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎりはいつどうぞー
Onigiri, here's an onigiri for you~
きらきら ふらふら しゃ～ない猫だもん
Sparkling, wobbling, can't help being a cat!
ふーん そっかぁ 僕でよくない？
Hmm, is that so? Isn't me fine?
まったり ゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Relaxed, leisurely, bouncing rhythm,
全肯定するおかゆイズム
All-approving Okayuism.
全行程効率OK
All processes efficiency OK,
毎日僕といっしょ！
Together with me every day!
(ころね)
(Korone)
おあっょ～ ゆびゆび ワンワン
Oh-yo~ Yubi-yubi, bow-wow!
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel,
懐く けど 圧かける
Affectionate, but applying pressure!
迸るインテンション
Overflowing intention,
割れるリアクション
Shattering reaction.
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信ショー
First, will you offer your fingers? Streaming show!
わがかったー ほーね 指示厨おけ
Got it~ Ho-ne, backseaters okay.
好物のレトロゲーお届け
Delivering favorite retro games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高
With all four, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
When a flag is set, collect it immediately!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and shoot straight,
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll restore your heart too!
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
Exciting, isn't it, this dungeon?
“耐久”っていうか止められない
Not 'endurance', just can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we just love games!
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点をお狙いしましょう！」
"Surprise! It's bonus challenge time. Let's respond loudly for a high score!"
(are you ready ?)
(Are you ready?)
say ! こーんこーんっ！
Say! Kon-kon!
(こーんこーんっ！)
(Kon-kon!)
say ! みおーんみおーんっ！
Say! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーんみおーんっ！)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
say ! もごっもごっ！
Say! Mogu-mogu!
(もごっもごっ！)
(Mogu-mogu!)
say ! ゆびっゆびっ！
Say! Yubi-yubi!
(ゆびっゆびっ！)
(Yubi-yubi!)
say ! こーんこーんっ！
Say! Kon-kon!
(こーんこーんっ！)
(Kon-kon!)
say ! みおーんみおーんっ！
Say! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーんみおーんっ！)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
say ! もごっもごっ！
Say! Mogu-mogu!
(もごっもごっ！)
(Mogu-mogu!)
say ! ゆびっゆびっ！
Say! Yubi-yubi!
(ゆびっゆびっ！)
(Yubi-yubi!)
(perfect !)
(Perfect!)
「おう～！」
Ooh~!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくてもコンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue!
全クリアするまで諦めない
Don't give up until full clear,
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices, simulation,
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Gaming is really fun, huh?
(G-A-M-E-R-S) we are gamers !
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers!
いっくよー もぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Here we go, mogu-mogu~ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎりはいつどうぞー
Onigiri, here's an onigiri for you~
きらきら ふらふら しゃ～ない猫だもん
Sparkling, wobbling, can't help being a cat!
ふーん そっかぁ 僕でよくない？
Hmm, is that so? Isn't me fine?
まったり ゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Relaxed, leisurely, bouncing rhythm,
全肯定するおかゆイズム
All-approving Okayuism.
全行程効率OK
All processes efficiency OK,
毎日僕といっしょ！
Together with me every day!
おあっょ～ ゆびゆび ワンワン
Oh-yo~ Yubi-yubi, bow-wow!
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel,
懐く けど 圧かける
Affectionate, but applying pressure!
迸るインテンション
Overflowing intention,
割れるリアクション
Shattering reaction.
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信ショー
First, will you offer your fingers? Streaming show!
わがかったー ほーね 指示厨おけ
Got it~ Ho-ne, backseaters okay.
好物のレトロゲーお届け
Delivering favorite retro games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高
With all four, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
When a flag is set, collect it immediately!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and shoot straight,
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll restore your heart too!
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
Exciting, isn't it, this dungeon?
“耐久”っていうか止められない
Not 'endurance', just can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we just love games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくてもコンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue!
全クリアするまで諦めない
Don't give up until full clear,
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices, simulation,
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Gaming is really fun, huh?
(G-A-M-E-R-S) we are gamers !
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers!
こーん！とキツネが登場
Kon! A fox appears,
白髪ケモミミ 白上フブキ です
White-haired kemonomimi, Shirakami Fubuki!
スッとん込んでちゃ始まらない
Can't start without rushing in!
君もスコン部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sconbu too!
hi friends !
Hi friends!
古今東西こうん茶をちょっとだい
A cup of Kohun tea from past and present,
AIじゃないし得意はMC
Not AI, and my forte is MC!
赤い恋より金色の鯉が推し
More than red romance, golden carp is best!
うちうちうちだょ 大神ミオだよ
That's right, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ 狼みおーん！
Black-haired kemonomimi, wolf Mio-n!
ツッコんで止めますlike a ママ
Stopping the tsukkomi like a mama,
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop, gege
つまり実はponってコト！？
Meaning I'm actually a bit pon!?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of quick little steps,
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future through tarot cards.
ホラーゲームはやしたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点をお狙いしましょう！」
"Surprise! It's bonus challenge time. Let's respond loudly for a high score!"
(are you ready ?)
(Are you ready?)
say ! こーんこーんっ！
Say! Kon-kon!
(こーんこーんっ！)
(Kon-kon!)
say ! みおーんみおーんっ！
Say! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーんみおーんっ！)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
say ! もごっもごっ！
Say! Mogu-mogu!
(もごっもごっ！)
(Mogu-mogu!)
say ! ゆびっゆびっ！
Say! Yubi-yubi!
(ゆびっゆびっ！)
(Yubi-yubi!)
say ! こーんこーんっ！
Say! Kon-kon!
(こーんこーんっ！)
(Kon-kon!)
say ! みおーんみおーんっ！
Say! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーんみおーんっ！)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
say ! もごっもごっ！
Say! Mogu-mogu!
(もごっもごっ！)
(Mogu-mogu!)
say ! ゆびっゆびっ！
Say! Yubi-yubi!
(ゆびっゆびっ！)
(Yubi-yubi!)
(perfect !)
(Perfect!)
「おう～！」
Ooh~!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくてもコンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue!
全クリアするまで諦めない
Don't give up until full clear,
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices, simulation,
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Gaming is really fun, huh?
(G-A-M-E-R-S) we are gamers !
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers!
こうして世界に平穏が訪れたのであった――
And thus, peace came to the world--
はーい、ということで始まりましたー！
Hi everyone, and so it's started!
すごいね、
It's amazing,
ここはライブゲーマーズ 超超超ゲーマーズ2です！
This is Live Gamers, Chou Chou Chou Gamers 2!
はーい、じゃあちょっとね、自己紹介やっていきますかね。
Alright, shall we do some self-introductions?
はい、みなさん、こんこんきつね！
Hi everyone, Konkon Kitsune!
白上フブキです、よろしくお願いします！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki, nice to meet you!
そしてね、もう1曲目はVアゲーマーズやらしてもらったんですけど、ついに4人というところで、いるじゃないですか、4人が。
And for our first song we performed V-Gamers, but now there are finally four of us here, aren't there?
はい、大神ミオです！
Hi, I'm Ookami Mio!
おつみお！おつだよー！
Otsumio! Otsu dayo!
おかみおのみなさんいらっしゃいませー！
Welcome, everyone in the Okamio audience!
猫又おかゆです、よろしくお願いします！
I'm Nekomata Okayu, nice to meet you!
今日はね、最高の思い出を作って、楽しんでいっちゃおう！
Today, let's make the best memories and have a great time!
はい、ゆびゆびー！戌神ころねです、よろしくお願いします！
Hi, Yubi-yubi! I'm Inugami Korone, nice to meet you!
みんな今日は、大事な日なの、何の日か知ってる？
Everyone, today is a very special day. Do you know what day it is?
今日はね、大神ミオの誕生日ー！
Today is Ookami Mio's birthday!
ということで、戌神ころねです、よろしくお願いしまーす！
That aside, I'm Inugami Korone, nice to meet you!
てことでね、改めてまして、4人揃っての、Vゲーマーズ、超超超ゲーマーズ2、そのDAY1こそ、さいたまスーパーアリーナでのゲーマーズでございます！
So, to reintroduce ourselves, all four of us together—Chou Chou Chou Gamers 2, on DAY1 right here at Saitama Super Arena, this is Gamers!
すごいなんとですね、DAY1 DAY2両日とも完売ということで、DAY1 DAY2共に約1万7千とかの皆さんが今日来てくださってる、そうです！
And amazingly, both DAY1 and DAY2 are sold out, with about 17,000 people attending each day!
びっくりした、運営さんから、DAY1 DAY2合わせて3.5万人くらいですって。
We were surprised when management told us it's about 35,000 people combined for both days.
すごすぎる！そんなにいるの？すごーい！人間じゃん！
That's amazing! There are really that many? Incredible! You're human!
昨年はね、国立代々木競技場第一体育館だったんですけども、今回はさいたまスーパーアリーナということで、すごいですよね、もう。
Last year we were at Yoyogi National Gymnasium, but this time it's Saitama Super Arena. It's amazing!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you!
さて改めてまして、このイベントはですね、ゲームが大好きな我々ゲーマーズを中心に、豪華ゲストと一緒に、様々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントです！
Now, to reintroduce it, this event is centered around us game-loving Gamers, where we take on various game titles with special guests and deliver live performances!
しかも今回は皆さんに、突然出てきて、え、3Dなの？って感じなんですけど、4人のお揃いの衣装をお披露目でございますよ！
And what's more, you were probably surprised when we suddenly appeared in matching 3D outfits for all four of us!
いやね、本当この衣装可愛いから着たいねって言ってたら、用意してくださいました、ありがとうございます！
We kept saying how cute these outfits were and that we wanted to wear them, and they made it happen. Thank you so much!
いや、本当可愛いですよね！ねえ、みんな見てるのー？可愛い、ありがとうございます！
They really are so cute! Everyone watching—aren't they cute? Thank you!
さらにですね、会場では一部撮影OKのパートがありますので、そちらではですね、ぜひスマホでお写真を撮っていただけると嬉しいです、ぜひ最後まで一緒に楽しみましょう！
Also, there will be a portion where photography is permitted, so we'd be happy if you could take photos with your phones. Let's enjoy the rest together!
てことですね、始まっていくんですけども、一人ずつちょっと意気込みお願いしたいと思いますよ！じゃあまず、ミオから。
So with that, we're going to get started, but first we'd like to ask each for a few words of enthusiasm! First up, Mio.
はい！
Yeah!
今年は…去年はね、ちょっとお休みしちゃったんですけど、
This year... well, last year we took a break, but
今年は4人でね、無事に開催することができたので、
this year we were able to hold it safely together as four!
ええ、明日も無事に終えられるように、
So that we can finish tomorrow safely too,
体調管理だけはしっかりして、明日とかを過ごしたいと思います。頑張るぞ！
I want to take good care of my health and get through tomorrow. Let's do our best!
大体いい感じ！がんばれ！
Looks pretty good! Do your best!
ではでは、続いては、おかゆ！
Now then, up next is... Okayu!
はーい！
Yay!
ま、僕はね、まあ、去年引き続いての参加となるんですが、
Well, I'm participating for the second year in a row, but...
ま、今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日ということでね！
Today happens to be Shohei Ohtani's birthday!
そういう人だけどさ、あのね、野球打率3割めざしたいと…
That kind of person, but um... I want to aim for a .300 batting average...
ちょっと手伝って！お願い！
Help me out a bit! Please!
はい！今日はね、翔平に素敵なプレゼントを届けられるように、
Yes! Today, so that we can deliver a wonderful present to Shohei,
届けられるように…せめて心に届けてくれよ！
so that it reaches him... at least deliver it to his heart!
せめて心に届けて！
At least deliver it to his heart!
心に届けます！
I'll deliver it to your heart!
そしてですね、白上はですね、皆さん、あの、昨年続きまして、
And as for Shirakami, everyone, continuing from last year,
なんとあの台本のあの、8割が白上が読み上げるということで、
unbelievably, about 80% of the script is read by Shirakami,
あの、前半、前半の載せてるところにきて、ずっと
um, the first half, when it gets to the posted part, the whole time—
文字だらけな、あ、そうなんです。
It's just full of text—ah, that's right.
なので、噛み始めたら、あの、頑張ってるなと思って、いっぱいサイリウム振ってください。
So if I start stumbling, please think "she's doing her best" and wave your penlights!
なんですけど、お前らの恋には負けねえから、よろしく！
But! I won't lose to you guys' love, so look forward to it!
はい、そしてですね、今日と明日行われる超々超々ゲーマーズ2は、
Yes, and also, Chō-Chō-Chō-Chō Gamers 2 held today and tomorrow
ABEMAペイパービューで生配信してます！見てる？
is being live-streamed on ABEMA PPV! Are you watching?
見てるー！
We're watching!
あ、コメントもね、我々見えておりますよ。ねえ、ありがとうございます！
Ah, we can see your comments too. Thank you so much!
こちら配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！イベントが終わっても
Streaming tickets for this are currently on sale! Even after the event ends,
8月4日月曜日の23時59分まで何度でも見返すことができます！
you can rewatch it as many times as you like until Monday, August 4th at 23:59!
さらに、購入特典としましては、Day1とDay2で異なるシチュエーションの限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます！
Furthermore, as a purchase bonus, exclusive original voice dramas with different situations for Day 1 and Day 2 will be included!
で、Day1は秘密の事前プロデュースボイス…
Now, Day 1 is a secret pre-produced voice...
秘密って…これ、えっちなやつ？やばいかな、違います！
Secret... Is this an ecchi one? Is that bad? No, it's not!
そして、Day2は内緒の超甘え詰め合わせボイス…
And Day 2 is a secret, super-pampering voice assortment...
あれ、Day2のやつかな？やめな！
Wait, is that the Day 2 one? Stop it!
頑張って考えられた2つのボイス、えっちじゃないです！って聞いてくださ…
These two voices were put together with hard work—they're not ecchi! Please listen to—
あとですね、我々の直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像もついてきますのでぜひチェックしてください！
And also, live images with our handwritten messages are included, so please check them out!
さらに、昨年行われました超々超々ゲーマーズの
Furthermore, the digest of Chō-Chō-Chō-Chō Gamers held last year
ダイジェストがABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！
is currently available on ABEMA Premium!
昨年のもね、めちゃめちゃ面白かったので是非とも見てください！
Last year's was super fun too, so definitely check it out!
ええ、さらにさらに、イベント後にグッズの受注販売が開始します！
And furthermore, mail-order sales for event goods will begin after the event!
おお、ありがたいことにDay1のグッズがなんと完売らしく、皆さんありがとうございます！
Oh, thankfully, Day 1's goods seem to be completely sold out. Thank you everyone!
こちらグッズの受注販売の期間が本日の朝10時から
The pre-order sales period for these goods is open from 10:00 AM today
7月21日の23時59分までサイバーグッズストアにて受付中でございます。
until July 21st at 23:59 at the Cyber Goods Store.
ええ、そこと、あとですね、イベント限定グッズとしまして
And also, as an event-limited good,
アクリルパネルが追加されます！
an acrylic panel will be added!
の話を、あの、おとなしく聞けない生徒みたいになってます。
You guys are acting like students who can't quietly listen to a presentation.
じゃあ先生の話聞くからね！
Okay, we'll listen to the teacher's talk!
はい、さらにさらに、もうご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが、
Yes, and furthermore, as some of you may already know,
ローソンのコラボカフェも開催しました！
a Lawson collaboration cafe has also been held!
先生の話は聞かなくてもいいけど恋人は出さないで。
You don't have to listen to the teacher's talk, but don't bring up lovers!
ええ、今、Okayuの紹介してたでしょ？友達です。
Um, I was just introducing Okayu, right? We're friends.
じゃあ、入り口でもらったチラシは皆様ゲットしましたか?
Now, did everyone get...
the flyer at the entrance?
もらった方?
Did you?
もらったチラシも使って、念中賞大作戦を満点にして、
Please use that flyer to...
念中賞大作戦を満点にして、
make it a perfect success,
最後まで楽しんでくださいね!
and enjoy it all the way to the end!
満点大作戦!
A perfect success!
ちょっともうちょっとスピードを上げて、
Let's speed it up just a little bit more,
ね。
and...
まだまだ続きますよ。
It's going to keep going even more, y'all!
よっしゃー!
Yeah!
上下マパッチ、我々ゲモスを応援したいという声が多かったので、
For the "Jogekamapachi" game,
応援したいという声が多かったので、
we had so many people wanting to support us,
今回イベントで、
so for this event,
チアスポットさんとのコラボをすることができました!
we've teamed up with CheerSPOT!
イエーイ!
Yay!
これはすごい!
That's amazing!
会場内のね、これあのなんと、
And inside the venue,
ね、
you know,
スポットが我々になってまして、
that CheerSPOT became ours,
びっくりしました。
so we were really surprised.
そうなの。
Right?
見てないの?
Did you see it?
見てたよ。
See it!
We were seeing it.
見てたよ。
We were seeing it!
マネるやつか。
Imitating us, huh?
そうです。
Yeah.
そうだそうだ!
That's right!
会場内に確かめてたまいますので、よかったら見てください。
It's actually inside the venue, so be sure to check it out!
そしてさらに、
And furthermore...
さいたまスーパーリーナの会場内で堂々台を初おひろめ!
we're announcing the first-ever "Oushin-dai" inside the Super Arena!
3月のエクスプ会場で発表されました、ふぶみよのおうしんだいに続きまして、
Following the "Oushin-dai" announced at the March EXPO venue,
おかころまフィギュアも発売され、より揃って、
Ookami Mio figures will also be released,
イエーイ!
Yay!
事前にのごち配信ではさ、
In the prior private broadcast,
なかったら、あのおかニャンと毛玉なんじゃないかって言ってたんですけど、
we said that if they weren't there,
ちゃんと揃ってましたね。
it turned out they were actually complete!
揃ってたよね。
They were really cute!
めちゃめちゃ可愛かったです。
They really were, weren't they?
ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
そしてまた本日より、
And also, starting today,
新作のフィギュアのデザインここから中中開始です。
pre-orders for the brand new figure design will start right here!
イエーイ!
Yay!
かわいい。
So cute!
かわいいすぎる。
やっぱりね白かみとみも欲しいなという。
Yeah, we want Shirakami and Mio too, right?
こう思った。
We thought that, and...
そこ野 あなた!あなた!あなた!
Look at you, you, and you!
なんと超ゲマズ2の開催を記念して、
To commemorate the "Cho-Gamers 2" event,
期間限定で、フブミをいつ追加予約を開始じゃ!
the Fubumio extra pre-order will begin!
やったー!
Yay!
逃したよっていうのもね、あの何人かいく見かけましたので、
If you missed out on getting them before,
これを機会にぜひともご予約をお願いします。
please make sure to pre-order them this time!
お願いします。
Please!
そして最後に鎌倉様による共産企業グッズ、
And finally, we're introducing the...
超超超超ポップコーンと超超超超グリルチキンのご紹介でございます。
Chou-Chou-Chou-Chou Popcorn and Chou-Chou-Chou-Chou Grilled Chicken!
今回会のイベントのキービジュアルが全面的に出たデザインとなっているとのことです。
The event's key visual is featured in the all-over design of the package,
ポップコーンは税込み2000円で、
Popcorn is 2,000 yen,
缶バッジは税込み1500円での販売でございます。
and the badge is 1,500 yen including tax.
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、
The popcorn has a salty caramel flavor,
缶バッジはグリルチキン味になってます。
and the badge has a grilled chicken flavor.
誰か乗ってる。
Somebody joined in!
乗っかります。
Let's go together!
こちらのグッズは他のグッズと異なり受給生産ではなく数量限定商品の為、
These goods are limited quantity items, unlike other goods,
お急ぎください!
so please hurry!
集合アクリルパネルも含めて事後にしか購入できないグッズですので、
They are available for purchase only after the assembly acrylic panel,
皆様ぜひご確認ください。
so please make sure to check them out!
お願いします!
Please!
ちなみに今回は韓国でライブビューイングもやってるそうにしよう。
Also, this time, we're even doing a live viewing in Korea!
韓国の皆さん、アンニョンハセヨ!
Everyone in Korea, say "Annyeonghaseyo"!
アンニョンハセヨ!
Annyeonghaseyo!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you so much!
ではですね、いろいろご紹介も終わりましたので、
Well, now that we've gone through various introductions,
早速最初に行うゲームタイトルを発表しちゃいましょう!
let's finally announce the first game title!
おお!
Oh!
初めてのよ。
Are you ready?
よろしい?
Ready?
せーの、こちら!
Here we go!
ビビッダ!
Bibbidiba!
こちら、ルールは超簡単。
Now, the rules are super simple.
ミニゲームに対し、タイミングよくボタンを押してギリギリで止めるだけ。
Just press the button with good timing to stop it at the very edge!
なるほど、我々のですね、度胸を試す究極のビビリチェッカーゲームとなっております。
I see, we'll try out our own guts in this ultimate "Bibbidi Checker" game!
よりギリギリを攻めると、クールの評価がもらえそうです。
If you push it right to the very edge, you can get a "Cool" rating bonus!
今回はですね、我々個人戦でございます。
And for this time, we are doing individual matches.
1つのミニゲームに対して2人がそれぞれ挑戦します。様々な組み合わせで合計6ゲームを行お楽しみいただきたいと思います。
Each of us will try two mini-games, for a total of six games!
こちらはですね、我々のクールの合計数で1位を決めたいと思いますので、よろしくお願いしますよ!
We want to decide 1st place based on the total score of our "Cool" ratings, so let's do our best!
ではですね、ゲームを始める前に、なんと今回ですね、巨大コントローラーを用意してくれたということで、おお、紹介しましょう!
And before we start the game, we've actually prepared a giant controller for this time, so let's introduce it!
これでちょっと会場の皆さんも一緒に、はい、呼べよ!
Let's have everyone in the venue shout it out together!
巨大コントローラー!って叫んでくれると嬉しいです。できまーす!
"Giant Controller!" If you shout that out, we'd be so happy!
ゲームを巨大コントローラーで
We'll play games with a giant controller,
プレイしていくので皆さん、ここに来ますからね皆さん、行きますよ！
so everyone, we'll be coming right over here! Here we go!
せーの！いでよ！巨大コントローラー！
Ready, set... Appear, giant controller!
巨大コントローラー！
Giant controller!
ポンポンポンポンポンポン
Pam pam pam pam pam pam!
出た出た出た
It's out, it's out!
すごい早い早い
So fast, so fast!
いやーすごい！ちゃんとわれわれのマークになっている
That's amazing! It's actually our mark!
かわいい！かわいい！
So cute! So cute!
では、どの順番でチャレンジしていきますか？
Now, in what order will we take on the challenges?
我こそはというの
"I'll go first!"
ええ！？我こそは！？いや我こそは！じゃあでもみおしゃじゃないやっぱり
Eh?! You? No, me! Well, it's Mio-sha after all, right?
うわっ
Whoa!
おかえり
Welcome back!
みおしゃおかえり！
Mio-sha, welcome back!
やったほうがいって！やった！みおしゃお帰り！
You should go! Welcome back, Mio-sha!
じゃあ、みおしゃで、じゃあ続いては？
Okay, Mio-sha. Then what about next?
2人目！
Second person!
2人目やりたい？やりたいやりたい！
Do you want to go second? I want to! I want to!
じゃあ、ここで2番目えー！？
Then, here for second place... Eh?!
ごめん！ごめん！おかえり！お帰り！やだ！おかえり！
Sorry! Sorry! Welcome back! Welcome back! No! Welcome back!
じゃあおかゆ2番目！流れ的にね、ごめん
Okayu is second! Flow-wise, sorry!
3番目はどうする？ 3番目はだって3番目、これでどっちがいいよ。
What about third? Third... which one is better for this?
いや、鳥は嫌だ。3番手
No, the last performer is bad. Third place!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
なので対戦としましては1番最初は、みおしゃ！はい！みおしゃが対戦になります。
So for the matches, first of all is Mio-sha! Yes! Mio-sha will be participating in the match.
2番目ね！でことじゃあ順番決めていきましょう！
Second! In that case, let's decide the order!
順番ね！はーい！
Order! Yay!
えみおしゃさん、さあ僕が勝っても泣かないでね。
Mio-sha, now even if I win, don't cry, okay?
おかゆには何とか任せされてきてるし、この猫めちゃくちゃミニゲーム強いですよ！
Okayu has somehow managed to get by, and this cat is ridiculously strong at minigames!
そうだよね、ちょっと強いよね。強すぎるまである
That's right, she's pretty strong. Almost too strong.
このゲームは初見だからさ、ね。そうだよね、初めてやるよ。いや、でも難易度が高すぎたってミニゲームの
This game is our first time playing, right? Yeah, we're playing for the first time. Well, but the minigame difficulty was way too high.
確かにそれはあるかも。あー、だからね、なるべくでもそこでうちが勝ったらめちゃくちゃ奇跡的ってことでしょう？
That's true, maybe. Ah, so if I win there, it would be a huge miracle, right?
ええ？そんなカップル！？そんなカップル！？どうしよう、どうしよう！じゃあやっていきまーす！
Eh? What kind of couple?! What kind of couple?! What should I do? Okay, let's do it!
はーい！ここからいろいろゲームあるんですけど、まずは「シレンの２」というものをやっていこうかなと。
Okay! There are various games from here, but first we're going to play "Shiren 2".
おます。これ、さっきのね、スタッフさんがやったんですけど、スタッフさんが強すぎる。確かに、私ちょっとどんな感じかするんですけども。
I think so. The staff played this earlier, and the staff is way too strong. That's true, I wonder how it feels.
じゃあ準備いいですか、みお？はい！
So are you ready, Mio? Yes!
はい、それではいきますよ！
Okay, here we go!
頑張れよー！いってらっしゃい！
Do your best! Have fun!
大得点！マスター、あちらの美しい女性に一杯。
Big score! "Master, a drink for the beautiful lady over there."
なるほどね！かしこまりました！かしこまりました！なんだこいつの顔！かしこまりました！
I see! Understood! Understood! What's with this guy's face? Understood!
じゃあクリックすると、はい、まずは練習ですね。練習ね、はい。グラスをすべらせろ！
Clicking it... okay, first is practice. Practice, yes. Slide the glass!
はい、クリックやってみたいと思います。あ、左にゲージがある。どうやら長押ししてゲージを溜めるらしいの。
Yes, I'd like to try clicking. Ah, there's a gauge on the left. Apparently, you hold down to fill the gauge.
ことか！
Is that it?!
なんて言ったらいいんだっけ？ Goodですね、マスター。
What was I supposed to say? "Good, Master."
ええ！？こんなのだけいけないんでしょう？
Eh?! You can't just do that, right?
はい、それでは本番です！いきます！
Alright, now it's the real deal! Here we go!
ここだ！あ！待って待って待って待って！うわー！やったー！ COOL！！
Right here! Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait! Wow! Yay! COOL!!
クリアー！すっごい！
Clear! Amazing!
すごい、すごい、すごい！
Amazing, amazing, amazing!
真ん中でやりたい、おかゆ。真ん中でやりたい。まだ早い！真ん中から。そこか、そこか。そうだね。でもね、ちょっと早かった。
I want to do it in the middle, Okayu. I want to do it in the middle. Still too early! From the middle. Right there, right there. That's right. But well, it was a bit early.
任せてやれ！任せてやれ！
Leave it to me! Leave it to me!
ということで、みおは今50だったかな？50だよね。50というね。
So, Mio was 50 just now, right? It was 50. 50, right?
ということで、続いてはおかゆなんですけども、どうですか？
So, next is Okayu. How about it?
いけますか？自信あり。頑張ります！
Can you do it? Confident. I'll do my best!
頑張れよ！稼いでやれ！
Do your best! Earn big!
じゃあそれではいきますよ、おかゆのビビターズタートー！
Then here we go, Okayu's Viviter Start!
さて、おかゆも練習があります。レトロゲームの優しいね。
Now, Okayu also has practice. Retro game kindness.
かしこまりました！かしこまりました！
Understood! Understood!
練習、お願いします！はい！練習は、まずね
Practice, please! Yes! Practice is, first of all...
グラスをすべらせろ！
Slide the glass!
おい！いけるか？え？
Hey! Can you do it? Eh?
そこはVIVITERですよ、マスター。え？自分の注文じゃねえかそれ！
That's VIVITER, Master. Eh? Isn't that your own order?!
やばい！本番になっちゃった！
Oh no! It turned into the real deal!
本番だよ！がんばれ！
It's the real deal! Do your best!
待て待て、もう一回！
Wait, wait, one more time!
え、そんなお尻ふりふりじゃなくてさぁ
Hey, not with all that hip shaking...
怠けない、怠けないからね！
Don't slack off, don't slack off!
ほら、これで勝てませんかね？
Look, can't we win with this?
今の負け！
That's a loss!
なまけないでよ！なまけないでよ！
Don't slack off! Don't slack off!
ふざけんなぁ！
Are you kidding me?!
みおちゃん強かった！
Mio-chan was strong!
え、難しそうなんだよね、これね。
Man, this looks pretty difficult.
やあねぇ、嘘。
No way, seriously?
と言うことでみなさん、こちら突然ではございますが、一斉でお知らせでございます！
That being said everyone, out of the blue, we have an announcement to make simultaneously!
なんと、無料配信をご覧の皆さんはここまでとなります！
Surprisingly, for those watching the free stream, this is where we part ways!
えーー！つづきをご覧になりたい方は
Eeee?! For those who want to watch the continuation,
ぜひABEMA PPVにてチケットのご購入をお願いします！
please purchase tickets on ABEMA PPV!
お願いしまーす！バイバーイ！
Please do! Bye-bye!
あっさり！バイバーイ！バイバーイ！
So simple! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
ばいばーい！
Bye-bye!
ね、これからもね、あの、めちゃめちゃ楽しいゲームね、ゲストもいるのでね。
Also, from now on, there'll be super fun games and guests too,
はい、楽しんでいただけると嬉しいです。よろしくお願いしまーす！
so we hope you enjoy it. Thank you very much!
それでは、行ってきまーす！バイバーイ！ばいばーい！
Well then, we're off! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
甘い！ふうー！
Sweet! Woo!
無料パートは終了いたしました 全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
[The free portion has ended. The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!]
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free section has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
Watch the full version on ABEMA PPV!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full version can be viewed on ABEMA PPV!